

Full Stack Developer

Los Angeles, CA (715) 441 1884 jacobkmiller@icloud.com www.jacobkmiller.com

Full Stack Web Developer specializing in back end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including JavaScript, Python and Ruby.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python

Ruby

**Javascript** 

HTML5

CSS3

Jquery

Node.js

Express.js

Angular.js

MongoDB/Mongoose

MySQL

**PostgreSQL** 

Django

Rails

Github

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Fast Learning Organization Problem Solving Teamwork

## **EDUCATION**

2009 - 2013

B.A. in Environmental Science U.C. Santa Barbara

#### LINKS

PORTFOLIO

www.jacobkmiller.com

GITHUB

https://github.com/Jacobkmiller

#### LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jake-miller-32908445

## **PROJECTS**

**DOC 2 DOC** (October 2016 – Present)

**Description:** Rental Web App Providing a forum for the lending and renting of medical equipment between licensed professionals.

**Built With:** Ruby on Rails, Google Maps Javascript API, JQuery, JQuery UI, PostgreSQL, Materialize, Stripe API **Role:** 

- Generated backend functionality.
- Implemented Google Maps Javascript API
- Customized JQuery UI Datepicker
- Incorporated Stripe API

### **DRONE SQUAD** (September 2016)

**Description:** Social Web App for Drone Enthusiasts. **Built With:** Node.js, Express, Mongoose/MongoDB, Angular.js, Materialize, Google Maps Javascript API, Instagram API **Role:** 

- Built backend API to serve data to Angular app.
- Made CRUD functionality for Users, Events, and Groups.
- Incorporated Instagram API into our Angular app

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **TEACHING ASSISTANT - CODING DOJO** (December 2016)

- Address student questions
- Present demonstrations.

## **FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER** (October 2016 - Present)

- Interface with clients to determine project requirements.
- Develop custom websites using varying technologies

# **ENVIRONMENTAL SPECIALIST - ST.CROIX ENVIRONMENTAL** (2013 - 2016 )

- Created, edited and analyzed geographic data
- Updated/produced maps for contaminated sites
- Updated/Maintained our geographic database
- Collected data in field such as GPS and water samples